Finding Aid for the Herbert M. Webster Photographs, 1926-1955 MS.3338
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
Herbert M. Webster Photographs
1926-1955 (bulk 1932-1937)
MS.3338
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
1.5 Linear feet
This collection houses approximately 500 photographs that Herbert Webster took while hiking in the Great Smoky Mountains prior to the establishment of the Great Smoky Mountains National Park. Among the subjects most frequently depicted are House Mountain, Grandfather Mountain, Three Forks, Greenbrier Pinnacle, Rainbow Falls, Ramsey Cascades, Clingman's Dome, Siler Bald, Mt. Guyot, Mt. Cammerer, Mt. LeConte, Cades Cove, Bald Falls, and the Chimneys. The vast majority of these images are photographic negatives, but a few have accompanying prints.
Webster, Herbert M., (Herbert Merideth), 1908-1994
Conditions Governing Access
Colletions are stored offsite, and a minimum of 24 hours is needed to retrieve these items for use. Researchers interested in consulting any of the collections are advised to contact Special Collections at special@utk.edu.
Acquisition Note
This collection is property of the University of Tennessee Libraries, Knoxville, Special Collections.
Biographical/Historical Note
Herbert Merideth Webster was born to John Corum and Ida Dena (Cunningham) Webster on November 14, 1908. He was the fifth of five children, including Marjorie Inez (who married Walter Sanders on October 11, 1934), Katherine Agnes (who married Wayne O. Thompson), Maurice C. (who married Thelma Louise Russel on June 8, 1935), and Mildred (who married Alan Miller Jr. on July 3, 1937). John Webster was a professor and founded a school near Oliver Springs, Tennessee in addition to operating a printing press. Dena (Cunningham) Webster was a descendant of the pioneer families of Mossy Creek (Jefferson County) Tennessee.
Herbert Webster graduated from Central High School and later completed accounting courses at Knoxville Business College and at the University of Tennessee. He began working for the House-Hasson Hardware Company in about 1926 and served as treasurer, director, and credit manager before retiring in 1976. Webster was also very active in the Central Baptist church of Fountain City, teaching Sunday School, leading the Royal Ambassadors program, and helping to establish Camp Bayoca. In addition to his professional activities, Webster was an avid hiker and often participated in excursions with such prominent figures as A. G. Dutch Roth, Harvey Broome, Tom Brightwell, and Charlie Gibson.
Webster married Edith Mildred Tillett (1913-2000) and had three children: Clayton, Stephen, and Martin. He died on April 16, 1994 in Knoxville, Tennessee and was buried in Greenwood Cemetery.
Scope and Contents Note
This collection houses approximately 500 photographs that Herbert Webster took while hiking in the Great Smoky Mountains prior to the establishment of the Great Smoky Mountains National Park. Among the subjects most frequently depicted are House Mountain, Grandfather Mountain, Three Forks, Greenbrier Pinnacle, Rainbow Falls, Ramsey Cascades, Clingman's Dome, Siler Bald, Mt. Guyot, Mt. Cammerer, Mt. LeConte, Cades Cove, Bald Falls, and the Chimneys. Some of the pictures show Webster's fellow hikers, including Charlie Gibson, Tom Brightwell, Harvey Broome, A. G. Dutch Roth, June Thomas, Walter Cotton Clark, and Mildred Webster. The vast majority of these images are photographic negatives, but a few have accompanying prints.
Researchers should note that notes written on the original envelopes often refer to a print file and to a scrapbook that are not housed in this collection. Webster's image titles (including spelling) have been used whenever possible. Although many of the images are undated, most seem to have been made in the 1930s based on such factors as the names used for various geographical features.
Arrangement
This collection consists of three boxes.
Subjects
Broome, Harvey, 1902-1968; Roth, Albert, 1890-1974; Smoky Mountains Hiking Club of Knoxville.; Grandfather Mountain (N.C.) -- Pictorial works.; Great Smoky Mountains (N.C. and Tenn.) -- Pictorial works.; Greenbrier (Tenn.) -- Pictorial works.; LeConte, Mount (Tenn.)
Container List
- Old Chisholm Tavern, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Dutch Roth & Gail Edmondson (Frizzell), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- #1: House Mountain, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- #2: Charlie [Gibson] at Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- #3: Hikers in the fog Near Jump-Off ([Harvey] Broome - Ford - [Dutch] Roth - Niles), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- #4: State Line from Greenbrier Cove, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- #5: Mt. Chapman, 1934 September 23; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- #6: Gail Edmondson [Frizzell] hiking Grandfather Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- #7: Trail Between Gant Lot & Crest of Gregory, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- #8: Sister Mildred - House Mountain, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- #9: View from House Mountain, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- #10: Three Forks. Trip With Chas. Gibson & Tom Brightwell, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- #11: Charles Gibson at Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- #12: Arriving at Three Forks. Chas. Gibson, Tom Brightwell, Herb Webster. Shack Owned by Tom Alexander, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- #13: House Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- #14: House Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- #15: Fisherman's Shack. Three Forks - Spent the night in this Cabin with Charley [Gibson] and Tom [Brightwell], undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- #16: Cabin at Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- #17: Pool at Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- #18: Pool at Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- #19: Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- #20: Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- #21: Cold! Pool at Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- #22: Br-r. Three Forks. Charlie Gibson and Tom Brightwell, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- #23: Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 25)
- #24: Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 26)
- #25: Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 27)
- #26: Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 28)
- #27: Cabin at Three Forks, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 29)
- #28: Hike Jump-off from Brushy, 1934 August 15; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 30)
- #29: [Tom] Brightwell and Grogan looking toward Mt. Mitchell from Grandfather. Greenbrier Pinnacle, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 31)
- #30: This appears to be Greenbrier Pinnacle. Picture taken from the area above the Cabin before it was over-grown, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 32)
- #31: Hikers in the fog, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- #32: Wooly Top from Road to Greenbrier (near Palmer Center), 1934 June 23; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- #33: Little Pigeon from Near Pittman Center, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 35)
- #34: Odd tree formation on State Line near Laurel Top, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 36)
- #35: Rain Nearing the Chimneys, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 37)
- #36: Under-shot mill. LeConte Creek-Cherokee Orchard, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 38)
- #37: LeConte Lodge, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 39)
- #38: Bobcat on Frozen Head, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 40)
- #39: Early pictures of Alum Cave. Descent & ascent was [sic] made by wire cable at far end of overhang, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 41)
- #40: Contains neg. of stream in Greenbrier or Chilhowee. No. 40 is note on print of Haw Knob, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 42)
- #41: Old Barn in Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 43)
- #42: Bald River Falls. Tellico Area, undated; (Print) (Box 1, Folder 44)
- #43: Mt Guyot from White Rod, 1934 August 3; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 45)
- #44: Spec. End view of Fain Cabin. Trip to Haw Knob, 1934; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 46)
- #45: Tower on Mt. Sterling, 1934 September 2; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 47)
- #46: Find Dutch [Roth] in picture?, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 48)
- #47: The Ganz Lot. Gregory, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 49)
- #48: Ramsey Cascade, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 50)
- #49: Nice view of chimneys from highway, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 51)
- #49: Nice view of chimneys from highway, undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 52)
- #50: State Line near Strattons Meadow, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 53)
- #51: Harriet Foulkes (Koutnik) at Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 54)
- #52: Mt. Sterling from State Line near Low Gap, 1934 August 3; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 55)
- #53: Fain Ranch (View from the Ridge), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 56)
- #54: Little Pigeon from bridge leading to Chimney Top Trail, 1934 June 10; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 57)
- #55: State Line from Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 58)
- #56: White Rock from Low Gap, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 59)
- #56: White Rock from Low Gap, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 60)
- #57: Dutch [Roth] in Lead. Between Low Gap & White Rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 61)
- #58: Gnadian Family at Cherokee, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 62)
- #59: Under shot mill at Cherokee Orchard, 1932 July; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 63)
- #59: Under shot mill at Cherokee Orchard, 1932 July; (1 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 64)
- #60: Rainbow Falls. Masked down print of 116 neg., 1932 July; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 65)
- #61: Rainbow Falls. Virgie, Clyde, Maurice, John, 1932 July; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 66)
- #62: Old Mill in Claiborne Co. Near Tazewell. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 67)
- #63: Swinging Bridge near Sevierville, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 68)
- #64: Cove Mtn. in distance from Chimneys, 1934 June 10; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 69)
- #64: Cove Mtn. in distance from Chimneys, 1934 June 10; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 70)
- #65: Clingman's Dome from Siler's Bald, 1935 July 28; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 71)
- #66: Thunderhead from Siler's Bald. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 72)
- #67: Mildred (sister) on Grandfather Mountain, undated; (1 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 73)
- #67: Grandfather Mountain, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 74)
- #68: Spring House at Messer Cabin, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 75)
- #69: A log jam below Charlie's Bunion. Caused by floods following the fire in the Saw Teeth. [?] & June Thomas going over top. Walter (Cotton) Clark looks on, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 76)
- #70: Little Tub Mill. Cherokee Orchard, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 77)
- #70: Little Tub Mill. Cherokee Orchard, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 78)
- #71: Rainbow Falls where the falls are frozen from top to Bottom (Most views show the upper portion frozen and a cone building up at the bottom), 1933 February; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 79)
- #71: Rainbow Falls where the falls are frozen from top to Bottom (Most views show the upper portion frozen and a cone building up at the bottom), 1933 February; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 80)
- #72: Group at Major Campbell's prior to Grandfather Mtn. climb, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 81)
- #73: Windrock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 82)
- #74: Charley's Bunion From Dry Sluice Gap, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 83)
- #76: Shy Wood Creatures [Harvey Broome, Dutch Roth, and Tom Brightwell]. State line near Low Gap (near White Rock), 1934 August 3; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 84)
- #76: Shy Wood Creatures [Harvey Broome, Dutch Roth, and Tom Brightwell]. State line near Low Gap (near White Rock), 1934 August 3; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 85)
- #77: State Line Between Clingman's & Siler's, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 86)
- #77: State Line Between Clingman's & Siler's, undated; (2 of 2); (Hand-Tinted Print) (Box 1, Folder 87)
- #78: Group at Major Campbell's, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 88)
- #79: Elijah Oliver Home in Cades Cove, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 89)
- #80: Sheep on Mt. Sterling, 1934 August 2; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 90)
- #81: Clingman's Dome from Tower on Blanket Mtn., 1934 October 14; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 91)
- #81: Clingman's Dome from Tower on Blanket Mtn., 1934 October 14; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 92)
- #82: Chapman & Guyot from trail to Fittified Spring. Wooly Tops in extreme right of picture, 1934 April 21; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 93)
- #83: Mt. Collins from Siler's Bald, 1935 July 28; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 94)
- #84: Citico Crick, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 95)
- #85: Cades Cove from Silers?, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 96)
- #86: Hikers on Trail to Grandfather. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 97)
- #87: Thunderhead from Gant Lot, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 98)
- #88: Rain nearing the chimneys, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 99)
- #89: Rainbow Falls. Very Special. Made with box camera, 1926 July; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 100)
- #90: From Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 101)
- #91: State Line from Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 102)
- #92: Looking East from Mt. Sterling. Two trips on Labor Day week-end. White Rock (Mt. Cammerer) and Sterling (long hot hike to Sterling), 1934 September 2; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 103)
- #93: Unidentified Vista, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 104)
- #94: State Line from Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 105)
- #95: Greenbrier Pinnacle. From trail to Porters Flats, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 106)
- #96: Chimneys. View from Road, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 107)
- #97: Vacation Camp Hikers on Brushy. Tom Brightwell, Hober Sisters (Atlanta), Harvey Broome, Miss Rutherford, Miss Griffith, 1934 August 15; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 108)
- #97 Vacation Camp Hikers on Brushy. Tom Brightwell, Hober Sisters (Atlanta), Harvey Broome, Miss Rutherford, Miss Griffith, 1934 August 15; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 109)
- #98: Mildred at double tree. Haw Knob, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 110)
- #99: Camp at Double Springs Gap. Gay - Harvey [Broome] - Geo. Barber - Walter Berry - Wiley Thomas - Dutch Roth. Very Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 111)
- #100: Bridge at Porters Creek. Often Photographed, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 112)
- #101: Mt. LeConte from Fighting Creek Gap, 1932 July 4; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 113)
- #101: Mt. LeConte from Fighting Creek Gap, 1932 July 4; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 114)
- #102: Wheat field near Pitman Center. Good, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 115)
- #103: Sheep at Willie Myers. Cades Cove, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 116)
- #105: Large group on way to Blanket Mtn. Mildred & Mitchie in Center, 1934 October 14; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 117)
- #105: Large group on way to Blanket Mtn. Mildred & Mitchie in Center, 1934 October 14; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 118)
- #106: Stream in Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 119)
- #107: Fain Cabin, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 120)
- #108: Charleys Bunion, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 121)
- #109: Guyot from State Line near White Rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 122)
- #110: Thunderhead from Gregory, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 123)
- #111: Frozen Head. 1st hike with the club, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 124)
- #111: Frozen Head. 1st hike with the club, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 125)
- #112: The Cabin unfurnished! Very Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 126)
- #113: Little Pigeon River at Pittman Center, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 127)
- #114: Guyot & Old Black from Mt. Sterling, 1934 September 8; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 128)
- #115: Laurel Falls. Good, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 129)
- #116: Thunderhead from Rich Mtn. Road, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 130)
- #117: Appears to be Thunderhead framed by trees on other side, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 131)
- #118: Trail to Gregory by way of Gregory Ridge. Hikers crossing foot bridge, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 132)
- #119: Thunderhead from Silers?, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 133)
- #120: Rain over Greenbrier Pinnacle soon to bury us on Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 134)
- #121: Looks like same type foreground as 126 [Laurel Top near Haw Knob], undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 135)
- #122: AT Marker between Line Gap & White Rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 136)
- #123: [?] looking down into Cades Cove from Thunderhead, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 137)
- #124: LeConte Lodge. Special. Snow. With Georgia Trail Club, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 138)
- #124: LeConte Lodge. Special. Snow. With Georgia Trail Club, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 139)
- #125: Saw Teeth & State Line from Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 140)
- #126: Laurel Top. Haw Knob Area, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 141)
- #127: English Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 142)
- #128: From Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 143)
- #129: Leconte from trail leading from Mt. Harrison, 1935 March 17; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 144)
- #130: The Bain, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 145)
- #131: Self at odd shaped tree near Strattons Bald, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 146)
- #132: Down Roaring Fork with Dutch Roth, Harvey Broome, Harris [?], & Sonny Morris, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 147)
- #133: Sheep at Standing Indian, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 148)
- #134: Little fall on Ekaneekle Creek on return from Gregory, 1934 November 4; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 149)
- #134: Little fall on Ekaneekle Creek on return from Gregory, 1934 November 4; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 150)
- #135: State Line, 1934 July 18; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 151)
- #136: Tub Mill on Ramsey Prong - Greenbrier. Special, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 152)
- #136: Tub Mill on Ramsey Prong - Greenbrier. Special, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 153)
- #137: Trio on Brushy, 1935 June 2; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 154)
- #138: Bald River Falls. Made on trip to Haw Knob, 1934 July 14; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 155)
- #138: Bald River Falls. Made on trip to Haw Knob, 1934 July 14; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 156)
- #139: Tub Mill on Ramsey Prong. Greenbrier. Rare - mill gone, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 157)
- #140: Porters Flats Creek, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 158)
- #141: Hikers descending the rough trail down dry Sluice Gap, 1935 August 11; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 159)
- #143: Ducks at Willie Myers. Cades Cove, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 160)
- #144: Large group who turned out for walk to Blanket Mtn. Mildred & Mitchie in center, 1934 October 14; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 161)
- #144: Large group who turned out for walk to Blanket Mtn. Mildred & Mitchie in center, 1934 October 14; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 162)
- #145: Clouds over Pinnacle at State Line from Brushy. Self in foreground, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 163)
- #146: Camp fire at cabin, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 164)
- #147: To Dry Sluice Gap, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 165)
- #148: Unidentified Vista, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 166)
- #149: Ramsey Cascades, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 167)
- #150: Tom [Brightwell] & his shirt full of apples. Vacation Camp at Greenbrier, undated; (1 of 5); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 168)
- #150: Tom [Brightwell] & his shirt full of apples. Vacation Camp at Greenbrier, undated; (2 of 5); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 169)
- #150: Tom [Brightwell] & his shirt full of apples. Vacation Camp at Greenbrier, undated; (3 of 5); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 170)
- #150: Tom [Brightwell] & his shirt full of apples. Vacation Camp at Greenbrier, undated; (4 of 5); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 171)
- #150: Tom [Brightwell] & his shirt full of apples. Vacation Camp at Greenbrier, undated; (5 of 5); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 172)
- #152: The Cabin in the Brier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 173)
- #153: Ramsey [Cascades]. Harriet Foukes, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 174)
- #154: Mt. Chapman - Guyot. Greenbrier, 1934 September 23; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 175)
- #155: Rough Day on the Chimneys, 1934 June 10; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 176)
- #156: Sheep, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 177)
- #157: Bald River Falls, 1934 July 14; (Print) (Box 1, Folder 178)
- #158: Greenbrier Pinnacle from Brushy. Nice rain clouds below, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 179)
- #159-160: Out on a limb! fallen log across rim of Ramsey Cascade. 70' drop!, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 180)
- #161: Unidentified Vista, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 181)
- #162: Over the Roof of a cabin in Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 182)
- #163: Herders Cabin [on] Gregory Bald. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 183)
- #164: Bald River Falls, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 184)
- #164: Bald River Falls, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 185)
- #165: Ramsey Prong. Drinkwater Pool, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 186)
- #166: Group on Grandfather Mountain, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 187)
- #166: Group on Grandfather Mountain, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 188)
- #167: Unidentified Vista, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 189)
- #168: Greenbrier Pinnacle, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 190)
- #169: Saw Teeth & State Line from Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 191)
- #170: Ramsey Prong above Cascades, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 192)
- #170: Ramsey Prong above Cascades, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 193)
- #171: Charlies Bunion, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 194)
- #172: Ramsey Cascades?, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 195)
- #173: Porters Crick, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 196)
- #174: Dutch [Roth] in the Lead. Between Low Gap & White Rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 197)
- #175: A Cabin in the Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 198)
- #176: What is it! (Haven't the slightest idea!). Haw Knob, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 199)
- #177: Mt. Guyot from State Line near White Rock, 1934 August 3; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 200)
- #178: Herders Cabin. Gregory Bald. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 201)
- #179: Bald River Falls, 1934 July 14; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 202)
- #179: Bald River Falls, 1934 July 14; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 203)
- #180: Group at Major Campbell's near Elizabethton, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 204)
- #181: Guyot & Old Black from White Rock, 1934 September 3; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 205)
- #182: Down Roaring Fork Waterfall. Harriet Fowlkes, Harvey Broome, Dutch Roth, Roy Beach, Sonny Morris, Herb Webster, 1934 February 4; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 206)
- #183: Cabin Construction, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 207)
- #184: Below Ramsey Cascades, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 208)
- #184: Below Ramsey Cascades, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 209)
- #185: State Line from Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 210)
- #186: Leconte Lodge. Trip with Ga. Trail Club, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 211)
- #187: [Mt.] Guyot from White Rock, 1934 September 3; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 212)
- #188: Trail to Hangover, undated; (Damaged Negative) (Box 1, Folder 213)
- #189: Unidentified Copse, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 214)